Guide to the Pennsylvania State University, Department of Animal Nutrition records 00044
Eberly Family Special Collections Library
- Experiments and Projects, 4
  - Experiment 259 B - Analytical Sheets, 1932 (Box 19)
  - Experiment 259 C - Analytical Sheets, 1932 (Box 19)
  - Experiment 259 C - Statistical Results, 1932 (Box 19)
  - Experiment 259 C - Utilization of the Energy and Protein of Rations …., 1932 (Box 19)
  - Experiment 259 C - Results of Analysis, 1932 (Box 19)
  - Experiment 259 D - Feed Record, 1933 (Box 19)
  - Experiment 259 D - Tables and Graphs, 1933 (Box 19)
  - Experiment 259 D - Analytical Sheets, 1933 (Box 19)
  - Experiment 259 D - Cystine (1st Draft of Report), 1933 (Box 19)
  - Experiment 259 D - Cystine References, 1933 (Box 19)
  - Experiment 259 E- Analytical Sheets, 1933 (Box 19)
  - Experiment 259 E - Tables, 1933 (Box 19)
  - Experiment 259 E - Feed Sheets, 1933 (Box 19)
  - Experiment 259 A,B,C,D,E (Log Book), 1933 (Box 19)
  - Experiment 259 F - Vitamin B (Log Book), 1933 (Box 19)
  - Experiment 259 F - Analytical Sheets, 1933 (Box 19)
  - Experiment 259 F - Daily Feed Records, 1933 (Box 19)
  - Experiment 259 F - Supplementary Tables, 1933 (Box 19)
  - Experiment 259 J - Tables, 1933 (Box 19)
  - Experiment 259 P and Q - Phosporous (Log Book), 1935 (Box 19)
  - Experiment 259 E - X-Rays, undated (Box 19)
  - Experiment 1016 - Analytical Data and Preliminary Tables, 1954-1955 (Box 20)
  - Experiment 1016 - Analytical Data, 1948-1950 (Box 20)
  - Experiment 1016 - Silage Data, 1952-1956 (Box 20)
  - Experiment 1016 - Cowan Thesis, 1951-1952 (Box 20)
  - Experiment 1016 - Analytical Data and Tables, 1951-1952 (Box 20)
  - Experiment 1016 - Preliminary Tables, 1948-1951 (Box 20)
  - Experiment 1016 - Alfalfa Ash - Preliminary Tables, 1949-1950 (Box 20)
  - Experiment 1016 - Alfalfa Ash - Analytical Data, 1949-1950 (Box 20)
  - Experiment 1016 - Alfalfa Ash - Final Tables, 1949-1950 (Box 20)
  - Experiment 1016 - Alfalfa Ash - Final Notes, 1949-1950 (Box 20)
  - Experiment 1016 - Periods 1-4 - Ventilation, 1950 (Box 20)
  - Experiment 1016 - Periods 5-8 - Ventilation, 1950 (Box 20)
  - Experiment 1016 - Treatment of Urine at Barn, 1948 (Box 20)
  - Experiment 1016 - Utilization of Amoniated Industrial By-Products and Urea by Sheep, undated (Box 20)
  - Experiment 1016 - Nutritive Value of Kentucky Bluegrass and other Grasses, 1948-1949 (Box 20)
  - Experiment 872 - Log Book, 1937 (Box 29)
  - Experiment 872 - Energy and Nitrogen og Steer Urine (Box 29)
  - Experiment 872 -Inspection Tables (Box 29)
  - Experiment 872 - Methane Factor (Box 29)
  - Experiment 872 - Air Analysis, 1935 and 1939 (Box 29)
  - Experiment 872 - Tables, 1939 (Box 29)
  - Experiment 872 - Fasting Tables (Box 29)
  - Experiment 872 - Feed and Excreta Sheets, 1937 (Box 29)
  - Experiment 872 - Periods 1-4 - Ventilation - Steer 11, 1937-1938 (Box 29)
  - Experiment 872 - Test Run - Ventilation - Steer 11, 1937 (Box 29)
  - Experiment 872 - Periods 1-4 - Ventilation - Steer 22, 1937 (Box 29)
  - Experiment 872 - Periods 1-4 - Ventilation -Steer 33, 1938 (Box 29)
  - Experiment 872 - Periods 1-4 - Steer 11, 1937 (Box 29)
  - Experiment 872 - Periods 1-4 - Steer 22, 1937 (Box 29)
  - Experiment 872 - Periods 1-4 - Steer 33, 1937 (Box 29)
  - Experiment 872 Tables, 1937 (Box 29)
  - Experiment 872 - Dynamic Effects of Body Nutrients and Net Energy Values, 1937-1938 (Box 29)
  - Experiment 872 - Analytical Results, 1939 (Box 29)
  - Experiment 872 - Temperature Averages (Periods 1-3 - Steer #11), 1939 (Box 29)
  - Experiment 872 - Temperature Averages (Periods 2 and 3 - Steer #22), 1939 (Box 29)
  - Experiment 872 - Temperature Averages (Periods 1- 4 - Steer #33), 1939 (Box 29)
  - Experiment 872 - Calibration of Air Analysis Apparatus, 1939 (Box 29)
  - Experiment 872 - Preliminary Tables, 1939 (Box 29)
  - Experiment 872 - Final Tables, 1939 (Box 29)
  - Experiment 871 - Partition of Average Daily Nitrogen Intake per Rat, undated (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 - Relation of Fat to Economy of Food Utilization, 1945 (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 - Rats and High Fat Diets, undated (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 - Fats in Relation to Caloric Efficiency, undated (Box 11)
  - Fat Symposium, undated (Box 11)
  - Pepsin Digestion, undated (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 R/S/T, 1948-1950 (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 (Rats) - Log Book #3, 1936 (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 E - Application of the Voris Method to Data, undated (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 E - Preliminary Tables, 1942 (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 E - Final Tables, 1942 (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 E - Irregularity of Fecal Excretion with Rats, 1942 (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 F -Protein Diets and the Body Temp. of Rats, 1947 (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 G - Feed Sheets, 1943 (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 G - Body Balance Experiments, 1943 (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 - W Tables, undated (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 - Y Feed Sheets, 1951 (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 - Growth Curves, undated (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 - W Feed Sheets, undated (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 - Z Feed Sheets and Tables, 1951 (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 - R Feed and Growth Records, undated (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 - W Rat Study, 1951-52 (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 - U Daily Record of Feed and Live Weight, 1950 (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 T - Daily Feed Consumption and Live Weight Sheets, 1952 (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 T and U - Drafts of Papers, 1952 (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 T - Negatives for Slides, 1950 (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 U - Tables, undated (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 T - Tables, undated (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 G/H/I - Log Book, 1943-1944 (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 H - Body Balance, undated (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 H - Vitamin Requirements, undated (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 I - Respiration Chamber, undated (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 I - Final Tables, undated (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 J - Casein and Rats, 1945-1946 (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 J - Prelim. Tables - Resp. Chamber, undated (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 J - Final Tables, undated (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 J/K - Weight Equivalents of Rations, undated (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 K - Feed/Rats, 1946 (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 K - Body Balances - Tables, 1946 (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 - Results of Analysis, undated (Box 11)
  - Experiment 871 Q - Balance of Matter and Energy, undated (Box 11)
  - Experiment 259 H - Vitamin G (B2), undated (Box 12)
  - Experiment 864, undated (Box 12)
  - Experiment 260 - Log Book, 1931-1932 (Box 12)
  - Relative Precision of Meter Factors for Air Meters, 1956 (Box 9)
  - Experiment 249 Selected Sections, undated (Box 6)
  - Experiment 221 - Weight and Maintenance Requirements of Cows, undated (Box 50)
  - Experiment 221 -Period II - Animal # 615, 1916 (Box 50)
  - Experiment 221 -Period III - Animal # 615, 1916 (Box 50)
  - Experiment 221g - Cow # 887, 1922-1923 (Box 50)
  - Experiment 221 (Notebook), 1915-1916 (Box 50)
  - Experiment 221 (Notebook) (Previously Experiment 229), 1919 (Box 50)
  - Experiment 174 - Period 1, undated (Box 50)
  - Experiment 174 - Net Energy Values of Timothy Hay, undated (Box 50)
  - Experiment 179 - Net Energy Values of Red Clover Hay and Maize Meal, undated (Box 50)
  - Experiment 190 - Heat Production, 1905 (Box 50)
  - Experiment 209 - SO3 and P2O3, undated (Box 2)
  - Experiment 235 - Institute of Animal Nutrition, 1925 (Box 2)
  - Experiment 208 - Record of Adam's Use of Food (Notebook 141), 1907-1908 (Box 2)
  - Tankage Experiment, 1935 (Box 17)
  - Tobacco Experiments - Act and Leases, 1893-1902 (Box 53)
  - Experiment #130 - Tobacco Curing, 1895 (Box 48)
  - Experiment 208 and 209 - Methods used in Computation of Results, undated (Box 30)
  - Tobacco Experiments - Insurance on Leaf, 1884-1912 (Box 53)
  - Vitamin "B" Study (In Rats) - Nutritive Value of Bread, undated (Box 9)
  - Vitamin "B" Study (In Rats) - Energy Metabolism, 1934-1935 (Box 9)
  - Vitamin "B" Study (In Rats) - Utilization of the Nitrogen of Breads, undated (Box 9)
  - Vitamin "B" Study (In Rats) - Corn Rich Diet, undated (Box 9)
  - Experiment with the Respiration Calorimeter (Charts), undated (Box 14)
  - Prep Work for Respiration Calorimeter Experiment, undated (Box 17)
  - Experiments 212-216 - Ash Constituents, undated (Box 30)
  - Notes on various Experiments, 1915 (Box 30)
  - Dairy Project 713 (Works of the Institute of Animal Nutrition…….), 1926 (Box 55)
  - Programme of Experiments and Results, 1869-1879 (Box 56)
  - Experimental Feeding Records, 1907 (Box 58)
  - Feeding Records - Various Experiments, undated (Box 59)
  - The Efficiency of Utilization of Phosphorus by the Albino Rat, 1943 (Box 27)
  - The Efficiency of Utilization of Phosphorus by the Albino Rat - (Log Book), 1942-1943 (Box 27)
  - List of Projects, 1950-1958 (Box 17)
  - Experiment log books, circa 1890s (Box 83)
  - Experiment log books, circa early 1900s (Box 84)
- Financial, 5
  - Budget and Expenditures (NE-21), 1954-1955 (Box 17)
  - Budget and Expenditures (NE-24), 1955-1958 (Box 17)
  - Budget and Expenditures (NE-16), 1955-1956 (Box 17)
  - Wages General Chemical Research Grant, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Regional Research Fund Requisitions, 1958-1959 (Box 17)
  - Monsanto Research Grant Budget (Project 1016), 1953-1955 (Box 17)
  - General Chemical Research Grant Budget (Project 1016), 1953-1955 (Box 17)
  - Requisitions and Expense Accounts, 1953-1955 (Box 17)
  - Farm Account Books, 1868-1879 (Box 40)
  - Barn Books - Records of Sales, 1870-1874 (Box 40)
  - Tobacco Experiment Expense Accounts, 1904 (Box 51)
  - Tobacco Experiments-Accounts and Vouchers, 1893-1913 (Box 53)
  - Reports on Expenditures, undated (Box 53)
  - Executive of Estate/Hardman Phillips Accounts, undated (Box 53)
  - Chemical Bills and Invoices, 1901-1912 (Box 53)
  - Creamery Receipts, 1896-1907 (Box 53)
  - Financial Records - Trial Balances, 1881-1906 (Box 53)
  - Financial Statements and Correspondence from University Business Office, 1897-1913 (Box 53)
  - Freight Notices, Bills, Invoices, 1894-1908 (Box 53)
  - McCormick, J. Frank - Expenses, 1896-1897 (Box 53)
  - Invoices, Bills, Receipts, 1893-1904 (Box 53)
  - Expense Acc'ts; Appropriations; Salary info.; Letters and more, 1888-1899 (Box 53)
  - Account Book - (PA. State Colleg AG. Experiment Station), 1893-1894 (Box 54)
  - Account Book - (PA. State Colleg AG. Experiment Station), 1899-1906 (Box 54)
  - Cash Book, 1888-1905 (Box 54)
  - Account Book (check book stubs), 1888-1901 (Box 54)
- Glass Lantern Photographic Slides, 6
  - Slides - Milk House, undated (Box 37)
  - Slides - unidentified, undated (Box 37)
  - American Farm Home: How to Make Its Work Easier, 1923; Photographic Slides Glass Lantern (Box 61)
  - How to Grow Potatoes, 1920s; Photographic Slides Glass Lantern (Box 62)
  - Tomato Growing, 1920s; Photographic Slides Glass Lantern (Box 63)
  - Alfalfa, 1920s; Photographic Slides Glass Lantern (Box 64)
  - Factors in Corn Production, 1920s; Photographic Slides Glass Lantern (Box 65)
  - Production and Distribution of Corn, Slides 1-51, 1920s; Photographic Slides Glass Lantern (Box 66)
  - Greater Profit From the Oat Group, Slides 1-52, 1920s; Photographic Slides Glass Lantern (Box 67)
  - Commercial Potato Production, 1926; Photographic Slides Glass Lantern (Box 68)
  - Culling the Laying Hen, 1920s; Photographic Slides Glass Lantern (Box 69)
  - Breeds of Swine, 1920s; Photographic Slides Glass Lantern (Box 70)
  - Swine Management, 1920s; Photographic Slides Glass Lantern (Box 71)
  - Cow Testing and Dairy Records, 1920s; Photographic Slides Glass Lantern (Box 72)
  - Production of Clean Milk, 1920s; Photographic Slides Glass Lantern (Box 73)
  - Fight the Fly, Slides 1-48, 1920s; Photographic Slides Glass Lantern (Box 74)
  - Fight the Fly, Slides 49-58, 1920s; Photographic Slides Glass Lantern (Box 75)
  - Greater Profit From the Oat Group, Slides 53-57 and Booklet, 1920s; Photographic Slides Glass Lantern (Box 75)
  - Production and Distribution of Corn, Slides 52-62, 1920s; Photographic Slides Glass Lantern (Box 75)
  - General Agronomy Slide Presentation, 1920s; Photographic Slides Glass Lantern (Box 76)
  - General Agronomy Slide Presentation and Miscellaneous Slides, 1920s; Photographic Slides Glass Lantern (Box 77)
  - Slide Presentations, undated; Photographic Slides Glass Lantern (Box 78)
  - Slide Presentations, undated; Photographic Slides Glass Lantern (Box 79)
  - Slide Presentations, undated; Photographic Slides Glass Lantern (Box 80)
  - Photographs
  - Slides of the Calorimeter, animals, and experiments, undated (Box 81)
  - Slides of the Calorimeter, animals, and experiments, undated (Box 82)
  - Slides of the Calorimeter, animals, and experiments, undated (Box 85)
  - Slides of the Calorimeter, animals, and experiments, undated (Box 86)
  - Slides of the Calorimeter, animals, and experiments, undated (Box 87)
  - Slides of the Calorimeter, animals, and experiments, undated (Box 88)
  - Slides of the Calorimeter, animals, and experiments, undated (Box 89)
- Notebooks/Record Books, 7
  - Notebook 4 Carbon, undated (Box 4)
  - Notebook Number 5B Moisture, undated (Box 4)
  - Notebook 6: Energy and Carbon, undated (Box 4)
  - Notebooks: Energy 6A - 6N, undated (Box 4)
  - Notebooks: Energy 6 O - 6 S, undated (Box 5)
  - Notebook 13A, 1946-1947 (Box 5)
  - Notebook: Experiments: 241, 249 and 261, 1929-1931 (Box 5)
  - Notebook: Ventilation Experiment 872, 1937-1938 (Box 5)
  - Notebook 14, 1937-1938 (Box 5)
  - Notebooks 14 A-F, 1938-1948 (Box 5)
  - Notebook I, 1924 (Box 7)
  - Notebook 3, 1927-1929 (Box 7)
  - Notebook # 5 - Moisture, 1925 (Box 7)
  - Notebooks 14 G - 14 I, 1942-1946 (Box 7)
  - Notebooks 14 J (pts. 1 and 2), 1944-1950 (Box 7)
  - Notebook 14 K, 1945-1947 (Box 7)
  - Notebooks 14 L (pts. 1 and 2), 1947-1950 (Box 7)
  - Notebook 14 M, 1950-1951 (Box 7)
  - Notebook #364 (Food Samples Reception), 1917 (Box 36)
  - Notebook #393, 1932-1933 (Box 36)
  - Notebook #367 (E.S. Erb) - Food, 1917 (Box 36)
  - Notebook #82 (McDonnell), undated (Box 36)
  - Notebook #280, 1910 (Box 36)
  - Notebook - Food - E.S. Erb, 1921 (Box 36)
  - Notebook #379, 1922 (Box 36)
  - Notebook #407 - Food, 1931 (Box 36)
  - Notebook #412, 1931 (Box 36)
  - Notebook #385, 1919-1921 (Box 36)
  - Notebook #521, 1936-1937 (Box 36)
  - Notebook #372, 1920 (Box 36)
  - Notebook #131 - General Fertilizer Experiment, 1905-1907 (Box 46)
  - Notebook #132 - Poultry, 1904-1905 (Box 46)
  - Notebook #133 - Cow Peas, 1904 (Box 46)
  - Notebook #136 - Analysis, 1911 (Box 46)
  - Notebook #137 - Protein Supply of Dairy Herd, 1904-1906 (Box 46)
  - Notebook #138 - Nitro-Culture Bacteria, 1905 (Box 46)
  - Notebook #139 - Tobacco Station at Milton Grove, 1905 (Box 46)
  - Notebook #140 - Tobacco Experiments, 1903 (Box 46)
  - Notebook #142 - Soil Analysis and Experiments, 1904 (Box 46)
  - Notebook #144 - Potato Variety Tests, 1906-1907 (Box 46)
  - Notebook #149 - Tobacco Seed Selection, 1905-1907 (Box 46)
  - Notebook #150 - Samples, 1906-1907 (Box 46)
  - Notebook #151 - Germination Tests on Corn, 1906 (Box 46)
  - Notebook #152 - Seguminius Forage Crops, 1906 (Box 46)
  - Notebook N51 - Fertilizers, 1891 (Box 46)
  - Notebook N52 - Fertilizers, 1891 (Box 46)
  - Notebook N54 - Calorimetric Work, 1892 (Box 46)
  - Notebook N55 - Samples, 1891-1892 (Box 46)
  - Notebook #541 - Dormant Sprays, 1941 (Box 46)
  - Notebook #554 - Fermate Analysis, 1944 (Box 46)
  - Notebook #000 - Samples, 1907-1908 (Box 46)
  - Notebook R67 - Maintenance Feeding of Steers, 1894-1895 (Box 50)
  - Notebook R68 - Chemical, 1896 (Box 50)
  - Notebook R69 - Soil Temperatures/Calf Meals and Milk substitutes, 1895-1896 (Box 50)
  - Notebook R70 - Maintenance Feeding of Steers, 1896-1897 (Box 50)
  - Notebook R71 - Veal Production, 1901 (Box 50)
  - Notebook R72 - Samples for State Dairy and Food Commission, 1896 (Box 50)
  - Notebook R85 - Nutrition and Economy of Milk/Butter Production, undated (Box 50)
  - Notebook R86 - Nutrition and Economy of Milk/Butter Production, 1896 (Box 50)
  - Notebook R87 - Dried Brewers Grains and Cerealine as Dairy Foods, 1897 (Box 50)
  - Notebook R88 - Butter Cultures, undated (Box 50)
  - Notebook R89 - Dried Brewers Grains and Ceraline as Dairy Foods, 1897 (Box 50)
  - Notebook R91 - Nutrition and Economy of Milk/Butter Production, undated (Box 50)
  - Notebook R96-Feeding Experiments, 1899-1900 (Box 50)
  - Notebook R97-Fertilizer Prices in New York, 1898-1907 (Box 50)
  - Notebook R98-Tobacco Experiment Wysox Station, 1896-1897 (Box 50)
  - Notebook R99 - Nutriton and Economy of Milk/Butter Production, 1897 (Box 50)
  - Notebook R100 -Tobacco Experiment At Rocky Spring, 1895 (Box 50)
  - Notebook #162 (Carpenter), undated (Box 42)
  - Notebook #165 (Cook Darrow), 1902-1903 (Box 42)
  - Notebook #147 (Beistle), 1901 (Box 42)
  - Notebook #517 - Food, 1936 (Box 42)
  - Notebook #514, 1935 (Box 42)
  - Notebook #358, undated (Box 42)
  - Notebook #503, 1932 (Box 42)
  - Notebook #373, 1920 (Box 42)
  - Notebook #372 - Tomato Pulp, 1918 (Box 42)
  - Notebook #376 (Stadder), 1921 (Box 42)
  - Notebook #397 - Eggs and Chicks, undated (Box 42)
  - Notebook #394, 1926 (Box 42)
  - Notebook #346 (Bathgate), 1915 (Box 42)
  - Notebook #84 - Tobacco, 1893 (Box 42)
  - Notebook #382 - (2 studies - Milk and Oysters), 1923 (Box 42)
  - Notebook #386, 1924-1925 (Box 42)
  - Notebook #381, 1923 (Box 42)
  - Notebook #164 (Edmiston), 1903 (Box 42)
  - Notebook #519 - Wood, Leaf and Tobacco Samples, 1937 (Box 42)
  - Notebook #518, undated (Box 42)
  - Notebook #163 (Carpenter), 1904 (Box 42)
  - Notebook #161 (Pingree), undated (Box 42)
  - Notebook #516 - Hay Samples - Ash Data, undated (Box 42)
  - Notebook #117 (McDonnell), undated (Box 42)
  - Notebook #505 - Residue on Apples, 1934-1935 (Box 42)
  - Notebook #405, 1929 (Box 42)
  - Notebook #411, undated (Box 42)
  - Notebook #409, 1933 (Box 42)
  - Notebook #416 - Food Analysis Fee Schedule for Chemists, 1933 (Box 42)
  - Notebook #121 - Cider Vinegar, undated (Box 42)
  - Notebook #410 - Food, 1934-1935 (Box 42)
  - Notebook #395 - Food, 1927 (Box 42)
  - Notebook #502, 1933 (Box 42)
  - Notebook #357, 1917 (Box 43)
  - Notebook #353, 1902-1904 (Box 43)
  - Notebook #403, 1927 (Box 43)
  - Notebook #365, 1917 (Box 43)
  - Notebook #508 - Samples, 1935-1936 (Box 43)
  - Notebook #553 (Sprays with Adhesive), 1944 (Box 43)
  - Notebook #539 (Blue Ribbon Orchard), 1941 (Box 43)
  - Notebook #540 (Field Spraying), 1941 (Box 43)
  - Notebook #387 - Isolation of Amino Acids and Bone, 1927 (Box 43)
  - Notebook #363, 1917 (Box 43)
  - Notebook #401, 1923 (Box 43)
  - Notebook #389, 1924-1925 (Box 43)
  - Notebook #361, 1919 (Box 43)
  - Notebook #571, 1916 (Box 43)
  - Notebook #354 - Nitrification Studies, 1915 (Box 43)
  - Notebook #359, 1915 (Box 43)
  - Notebook #404, 1929 (Box 43)
  - Notebook #506, 1934 (Box 43)
  - Notebook #355, 1916 (Box 43)
  - Notebook #402 - Food Analysis, 1925 (Box 43)
  - Notebook #406 - Food Analysis, 1930-1931 (Box 43)
  - Notebook #356, 1917 (Box 43)
  - Notebook #388, 1925 (Box 43)
  - Notebook # 512 - Spray Residue Results, 1934 (Box 41)
  - Notebook # 525, 1938 (Box 41)
  - Notebook # 349, undated (Box 41)
  - Notebook # 131 - Feeding Stuffs, 1900 (Box 41)
  - Notebook R1 - Field Work, 1888-1889 (Box 41)
  - Notebook R2 - Field Work, 1888 (Box 41)
  - Notebook R3 - Soiling Crops, 1888-1889 (Box 41)
  - Notebook R4 - Weather Influence on Crops, 1888-1889 (Box 41)
  - Notebook R6 - Pasture Grass, 1888 (Box 41)
  - Notebook R7 - Nitrogen Supply in Corn, 1892 (Box 41)
  - Notebook R8 - Ensilage and Corn Fodder Experiments, 1889 (Box 41)
  - Notebook R9 - Weather Reports on Crops, 1888-1892 (Box 41)
  - Notebook R10 - General Fertilizer Experiments, 1888-1897 (Box 41)
  - Notebook #141 (Carter), undated (Box 41)
  - Notebook #140 (Pingree), 1902 (Box 41)
  - Notebook #415 - Food Samples, 1927 (Box 41)
  - Notebook #144 (Norris), 1901 (Box 41)
  - Notebook #531 - Cherry Leaf Measurements, 1939 (Box 41)
  - Notebook - Research 3, undated (Box 41)
  - Notebook #101 - Tobacco Experiments, 1896-1897 (Box 48)
  - Notebook #339 - Lab, undated (Box 48)
  - Notebook #205 - Samples, 1908 (Box 48)
  - Notebook #294 - Lab, 1912 (Box 48)
  - Notebook #289 - Lab, undated (Box 48)
  - Notebook #285 - Samples, undated (Box 48)
  - Notebook #287 - Moisture, 1911 (Box 48)
  - Notebook #23 - Fertilizer (Holter), undated (Box 48)
  - Notebook #25 - Fodder Sample Record, 1889 (Box 48)
  - Notebook #56 - Milk and Butter Fat, 1892 (Box 48)
  - Notebook #58 - Butter and Milk Analysis, 1892 (Box 48)
  - Notebook #104 - Nutrition & Milk/Butter Production, 1899 (Box 48)
  - Notebook R81 - Legumes as Nitrogen Gatherers, 1896 (Box 48)
  - Notebook #103 - Samples, 1899 (Box 48)
  - Notebook #106 - Lime Investigation, undated (Box 48)
  - Notebook #105 - Lime Inquiry, undated (Box 48)
  - Notebook R92 (Experiment 143) -Sugar Beets in PA, 1897-1902 (Box 48)
  - Notebook R94 - Nutrition & Economy of Milk/Butter Production (Exp.148), 1898 (Box 48)
  - Notebook R80 - Nutrition & Economy of Milk/Butter Production (Exp.139), undated (Box 48)
  - Notebook R77 - Planting Farm Crops at Different Depths, 1897 (Box 48)
  - Notebook R76 - Feeding Trial by Glasgow in Bellwood, PA, 1896 (Box 48)
  - Notebook R79 - Tobacco Curing, 1895 (Box 48)
  - Notebook #102 - Chemical Changes in Apple Juice to Cider & Vinegar, 1889 (Box 48)
  - Notebook #110 - Samples, 1901 (Box 48)
  - Notebook #109 - Bacteriological Test of Milk from Cow to Consumer, 1900-1901 (Box 48)
  - Notebook R74 -Vinegar Analysis, 1896 (Box 48)
  - Notebook R75 - Chemical, 1896 (Box 48)
  - Notebook #100 - Nutrition & Economy of Milk/Butter Production, 1898-1899 (Box 48)
  - Notebook R92 - Tobacco Experiment at Mariella & Rocky Spring, 1894 (Box 48)
  - Notebook R93 - Rye Meal/Corn Meal/Oat Feed in Milk & Butter Production (Exp.151), 1898 (Box 48)
  - Notebook R78 - State Dairy & Food Commission Samples, 1896 (Box 48)
  - Notebook #160 - Sumatra Tobacco Grown Under Shelter, 1906 (Box 40)
  - Notebook #161 - Cow Milker vs. Hand Milking (Exp. 211), undated (Box 40)
  - Notebook #162 - Experiment Reports, undated (Box 40)
  - Notebook #163 - Report of Experiments, 1907 (Box 40)
  - Notebook #164 - Report of Experiments, 1906 (Box 40)
  - Notebook #165 - Experiment Reports, undated (Box 40)
  - Notebook #166 - Experiment Reports, undated (Box 40)
  - Notebook #167 - Experiment Reports, undated (Box 40)
  - Notebook #169 - Soiling Crops for Dairy Cows, 1907 (Box 40)
  - Notebook - Chemical Lab (H.J. Patterson), 1888 (Box 40)
  - Notebook #11 - (George Stotler), 1888-1889 (Box 40)
  - Notebook N49 - Fertilizers (Fries), 1890 (Box 40)
  - Notebook #09 - Digestibility of Corn Meal, 1888 (Box 40)
  - Notebook #14 - Soil Temperature, 1887-1888 (Box 40)
  - Notebook #15 - Experiments, 1889 (Box 40)
  - Notebook #16 - Lab (Holter), 1889 (Box 40)
  - Research Notebook (Meyer), 1945 (Box 40)
  - Notebook #282 - Wire Fence Work, 1911 (Box 40)
  - Notebook #286 - Samples, 1917 (Box 40)
  - Notebook #173 - Fertilizer Analysis, undated (Box 40)
  - Notebook - Chloroform Experiment, undated (Box 40)
  - Notebook - Lab - Wm. Frear, 1901 (Box 40)
  - Notebook - Feeding Experiments, 1901-1902 (Box 40)
  - Notebook 4 A, 1938-1947 (Box 7)
  - Notebook #526 - Spray Treatments, 1938 (Box 44)
  - Notebook #569 - Toxicity Tests, 1947 (Box 44)
  - Notebook #536 - Cherries (Blue Ribbon Orchard), 1940 (Box 44)
  - Notebook #000 - Laboratory Spraying Experiments, 1942 (Box 44)
  - Notebook #570 - Fumigants, 1947-1949 (Box 44)
  - Notebook #558 - Adhesive Sprays (Thesis by John B. Harry), undated (Box 44)
  - Notebook #550 - Sprays and Samples, 1943 (Box 44)
  - Notebook #527 - Apple Orchard Treatments, 1938 (Box 44)
  - Notebook #552 - Fractionation, 1943-1944 (Box 44)
  - Notebook #572 - Toxicity Tests, 1948 (Box 44)